<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string name="app_name">SmoothComm</string>
    <string name="likes"> likes</string>
    <string name="comments"> comments</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="nutrient" >Planning a daily menu isn\'t difficult as long as each meal and snack have some protein, fiber, complex carbohydrates and a little bit of fat.

Here\'s what you need to know about each meal.

Eating breakfast will help you start your day with plenty of energy. Don\'t ruin your breakfast with high-fat and high-calorie foods. Choose some protein and fiber for your breakfast, and it\'s a good time to eat some fresh fruit.
A mid-morning snack is totally optional. If you eat a larger breakfast, you may not feel hungry until lunchtime. However, if you\'re feeling a bit hungry and lunch is still two or three hours away, a light mid-morning snack will tide you over without adding a lot of calories.
A mid-morning snack is totally optional. If you eat a larger breakfast, you may not feel hungry until lunchtime. However, if you\'re feeling a bit hungry and lunch is still two or three hours away, a light mid-morning snack will tide you over without adding a lot of calories.
Lunch is often something you eat at work or school, so it\'s a great time to pack a sandwich or leftovers that you can heat and heat. Or, if you buy your lunch, choose a healthy clear soup or fresh veggie salad.
A mid-afternoon snack is also optional. Keep it low in calories and eat just enough to keep you from feeling too hungry because dinner is just a couple of hours away.
Dinner is a time when it\'s easy to over-eat, especially if you haven\'t eaten much during the day, so watch your portion sizes. Mentally divide your plate into four quarters. One-quarter is for your meat or protein source, one-quarter is for a starch, and the last two-quarters are for green and colorful vegetables or a green salad.
A light complex carbohydrate-rich evening snack may help you sleep but avoid heavy, greasy foods or foods high in refined sugars.
</string>
    <string name="addcomments">comments added</string>
    <string name="internet">No Internet</string>
</resources>
